## Jessica Saunders Jessicas 3049@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/pub/jessica-saunders/a8/199/6a4

## Objective

To develop and further establish my professional career through continued education and practical hands-on experience. I aim to provide value to my employer through good work ethics and critical-thinking skills to overcome key challenges in the workplace.

## Experience

Holiday Inn Gwinnett Center, Duluth, GA

Front Desk Agent, January 2015-January 2016

- Provide excellent customer service in a fast paced environment
- Efficiently processing guest arrivals and departures
- Upselling room upgrades and add-ons

Soma Intimates, Norcross, GA

Sales Associate, May 2013-January 2016

- Provide personal service and recommendations to meet clients' needs
- Handle visual merchandising to increase client interest and impact sales
- Exceed daily and monthly sale quotas

Inspire Health, Atlanta, GA

Client Service Representative, June 2014-January 2015

- Scheduled clients and checking insurance benefits
- Collected payments for each visit

DeKalb Medical Heart Wellness Center, Decatur, GA

Intern, January 2014-April 2014

- •Monitored blood pressure and set patients on equipment
- Identified EKG abnormalities

UNG Student Health Services, Dahlonega, GA

Grant Worker, Nov. 2012-April 2013

- •Updated grant each month to fund Peer Health Educators program
- •Organized alcohol and drug education events for students on campus

## Education

Kennesaw State University, Marietta, GA, Graduation: Fall 2016 Graduate Certificate in Software Engineering Foundations MS Software Engineering (Graduation: tentative)

University of North Georgia, Dahlonega, GA, Graduation: May 2014

Bachelor of Science in Physical Education (Exercise Science)

GPA: 3.55/4.0